Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- B Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  Bethe, Hans A.; Bovay, H. E.; Brooks, Dorothy V. N.
- C Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  Carey, Henry A.; Carpenter, Walter S.; Catchings, Waddill. Campbell Soup Company; CBS Foundation; Chile.
- C Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  Class of 1916 Professorship.
- C Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  Cromwell, Oliver F. W.; Guggenheim, Harry; Cornell, William B.; Cornell, Ezra. Committee on Higher Education in New York State.
- Congressional Bills and Legislation. Pirnie, Alexander., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- D Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  Delta Gamma; Discrimination; Fraternities with restrictive clauses.
- E Miscellaneous., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  Elmhirst, Dorothy Whitney Straight. Esouire Maaazine.
- F Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  Ford, Henry; Fraser, Henry S.; Summerskill, John; Fryer, Jeffrey. Freshmen Center.
- Ford Foundation., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- G Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  Gannett, Caroline Werner; Garrett, Robert T. General Electric Company; General Foods Fund.
- G Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  Gibson, Edwin T; Fox, Edith M.; Gilchrist, Thomas B.; Goodwillie, Edward E.; Grasselli, Caesar A.; Griffis, Stanton; Gibson, Wilmoth.
- New York State Agricultural Experiment Station - Geneva. Heinicke, Arthur J., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 29-30)
- H Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  Haines, Charles E.; Haller, Margaret P. Delta Delta Delta; Fraternities; University of Heidelberg.
- H Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  Hollander, Carl F.
- I Miscellaneous., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  IBM; International Cooperation Administration.
- I Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  Institute of International Education.
- I Miscellaneous., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- I Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  International Association of Universities.
- I Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  Smith, Ralph C. Ithaca, New York; Ithaca College; Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants.
- J Miscellaneous., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  Javits, Jacob K. James Foundation.
- K Miscellaneous., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  Kaufmann, Eugene M.; Kirn, Hong Bom.
- L Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  Liberia.
- M Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  Mennen, William G.
- M Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  Murray, William N.
- N Miscellaneous. Newman, Floyd R.; Nichols, Benjamin; Noyes, Jansen., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- N Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- National Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  National Science Foundation.
- National Defense Education Act., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 46-47)
  Pusey, Nathan M.
- O Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  Oppenheimer, Frank. 01 in Foundation.
- P Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  Pew, Joseph N. Peru.
- P Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  Pirnie, Alexander. Phelps Dodge Corporation; Phillips Foundation; University of Puerto Rico.
- R Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  Rhodes, Fred H.; de Kiewiet, Cornelius W. Rockefeller Foundation.
- R Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  Rogers, Frederick R.
- S Miscellaneous., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  Saperstone, David A. Sardis Expedition.
- S Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  Statler Foundation.
- Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  Sloan, Alfred P.; Summerskill, John. Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration.
- Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 56-57)
- Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 58-62)
- T Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  Telluride Association; Teagle Foundation; Texaco, Inc.
- U Miscellaneous., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 64)
- V Miscellaneous., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  Verity, Calvin.
- W Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 66)
- W Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  Wright, Albert H. Westinghouse Educational Foundation; Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation.
- Y Miscellaneous., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Board of Trustees., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Cisler, Walker L.; Collyer, John L.; Dean, Arthur H., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Dean, Arthur H., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Dean, Arthur H.; Levis, J. Preston; Donlon, Mary H., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 72)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 73)
  Mitchell, Albert K.; Willcox, Walter F.; Scheetz, Francis H.
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee. Hanson, C. Arnold., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 74-75)
- Board of Trustees - Governor of New York. Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 76-77)
- Cornell University Library Board., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 78)
- News Bureau., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 79)
- Gifts., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 80-81)
  Foundation for Public Relations Research and Education; United States Steel Corporation.
- Gifts., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 82)
  Kaufmann, Eugene M. Nutrition Foundation; Shell Companies Foundation; Esso Education Foundation.
- Gifts., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 83)
  Olin, John M. Standard Oil Company; General Electric Foundation; Proctor and Gamble Fund.
- Gifts., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 84)
  Seley, Louis E.; Coors, Adolph; Iglehart, Robert H. Creole Foundation; Chase Manhattan Bank.
- Gifts., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 85)
  Day, Lee Garnett; Tschirky, Leopold. Ford Foundation; United States Rubber Company; Tea Council.
- Gifts., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 86)
  Dean, Arthur H.; Levis, J. Preston. Johnson Foundation; Macy Foundation; Ford Foundation; National Science Foundation; CBS Foundation; B. F. Goodrich Fund; Phelps Dodge Corporation; National Lead Foundation; Coca-Cola Company.
- Cornell University Council., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 87)
  Robertson, William R.
- Cornell University Associates., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 88)
- Vice President for Research., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Hastie, John W.; Wright, Theodore P.; Peer, Sherman. Advanced Research Projects Agency.
- Vice President for Business., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  Burton, John E.
- Dept. of Buildings and Properties., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  Weinhold, Julius F.
- Dept. of Residential Halls., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Residential halls and dormitories.
- Vice President for Student Affairs., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  Summerskill, John. North Campus.
- Office of the Director of the Budget., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  McKeegan, Paul L.
- Office of the Director of the Budget., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Office of the University Counsel., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  Meigs, Robert B. Hughes Hall.
- Office of Admissions., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Committee on Admissions., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 10-11)
  Corson, Dale R.; Summerskill, John.
- Office of the Registrar., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Office of the Controller., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  Peterson, Arthur H. Liberia.
- Office of the Controller., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Commencement., 1957-61 (Box 28, Folder 15-17)
- Fraternities and Interfraternity Council. Delta Kappa Epsilon., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- "Cornell Widow.", 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  Donson, Theodore B.
- Executive Board of Student Government. Kendrick, M. Slade. Cornell Student Code., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 20-21)
- Cornell University Library., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
  McCarthy, Stephen A.; Schullian, Dorothy. Olin Library.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  Madigan, Richard A.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  Madigan, Richard A.; Solinger, David M.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art. Madigan, Richard A.; Solomon, Alan R.; Kartell, John A.; Marks, A. Lester., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- University Faculty. Hanson, C. Arnold. Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- University Faculty Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  Palm, Charles E. Cornell Plantations; Committee on Botanical Resources and Needs; International Agricultural Development.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  Palm, Charles E. Agricultural Progress Days.
- Laboratory of Ornithology., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey Hortorium. Peters, H. W.; Hunt, Roy A., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  Elias, Robert H.; Blackall, Eric A. Humanities Council.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  Mineka, Francis E.
- Glee Club., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  Dept. of Music.
- Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  Peru.
- Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  Dobyns, Henry F.
- College of Engineering. Corson, Dale R.; Olin, Spencer T.; Rhodes, Fred H. Ford Foundation., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- New York State Veterinary College., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  Baker, Donald W.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Law School., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  Thoron, Gray; Wood, Franklin S.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  International Cooperation Administration.
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  Stiles, Jack E.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Graduate School of Nutrition., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- Graduate School., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  Boynton, Damon; Bronfenbrenner, Urie.
- ROTC., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 50-53)
- Ivy League., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 54)
- Ivy League., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  Griswold, A. Whitney.
- Ivy League., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 56)
- NROTC. Association of NROTC Colleges., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 57)
- ROTC. Hanmer, S. R., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 58-59)
- Newman Laboratory of Nuclear Studies. Wilson, Robert R. Synchrotron., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 60)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  Moffitt, Henry K.; Ross, Ira G.; Dean, Arthur H.
- Summer Session. Smith, W. A. Latin America., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 62)
- Social Science Research Center., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  Brayman, Harold; Roemer, Milton; Whyte, William F.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 64)
- Alumni Fund., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  Class of 1920.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 66)
- Scholarships and Grants., 1959-60 (Box 28, Folder 67-68)
- Messenger Lectures., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 69)
- State University of New York., 1960-61 (Box 28, Folder 70-71)
  Hamilton, Thomas H.; Kille, Frank R.
- New York State Education Dept., 1959-61 (Box 28, Folder 72-73)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1961-62 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  Bewkes, Eugene; Ingalls, Lester W.
- A Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 28, Folder 75)
  Aspinwall, Francis H.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Sweezy, Paul M. Advanced Research Projects Agency; African Students Organization; Dept. of Economics; Conservative Club.
- A Miscellaneous., 1958-63 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  Strauss, Lewis L. Atomic Energy Commission; Avalon Foundation.
- A Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  Mackesey, Thomas W.; Donlon, Mary H. American Civil Liberties Union; Committee on Student Conduct; American Council of Learned Societies; American Women's Association.
- Association of American Universities., 1957-63 (Box 28, Folder 78-82)
  Wilson, Logan.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1961-63 (Box 28, Folder 83-86)
  Harvill, Richard A.; Alien, Herman R.
- B Miscellaneous. Ball, William H.; Kahn, Alfred E., 1962-63 (Box 28, Folder 87)
- B Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 28, Folder 88)
  Bronfenbrenner, Urie. USSR.
- C Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 28, Folder 89)
  Carpenter, Walter S. Campbell Soup Company.
- Congressional Bills., 1962 (Box 28, Folder 90)
- C Miscellaneous., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 91)
  Chile; Common Market.
- D Miscellaneous., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 92)
  Siscoe, Frank G.; Domonkos, Imre. du Pont de Nemours & Co.
- E Miscellaneous., 1962 (Box 28, Folder 93)
  Eisenhower, Dwight D.; Evett, Kenneth. Eastman Kodak Company.
- F Miscellaneous., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 94)
  Federal Communications Commission; Ford Foundation.
- G Miscellaneous., 1961-63 (Box 28, Folder 95)
- G Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 28, Folder 96)
  Gilchrist, Thomas B.; Goldwater, Barry M.; Goodell, Charles E. General Foods Corporation; Committee on the Undergraduate Grading System.
- State University of New York., 1962-63 (Box 28, Folder 97)
- H Miscellaneous., 1961-63 (Box 28, Folder 98)
  United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare; Hu Shih Memorial Scholarshi] Fund.
- I Miscellaneous., 1961-63 (Box 28, Folder 99)
  University of Chile; Ithaca, New York.
- J Miscellaneous., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Johnson, Beverly.
- K Miscellaneous., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  I
- L Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  Leach, Harry; Weeks, Rochefort L.; Wright, Carl ton E.; Konvitz, Milton R. Latin America; Cornell Latin America Year; Liberia; University of Liberia.
- M Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  Mermen, William G.; Healey, George H.; Einaudi, Mario; Weiss, Ottocar; Ellmann, Richard. Dept. of Rare Books Joyce Collection; Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools; Morrill Foundation.
- National Association of State Universities., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- N Miscellaneous. Kennedy, W. Keith; Waterman, Alan T. National Institutes of Health; National Science Foundation., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- N Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  Kranz, Harry; Nolan, J. Bennett; Noyes, Agnes B.; Noyes, Jansen. National Science Foundation; United States National Service Corps (Proposed).
- P Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  Parmenter, Richard; Shriver, Sargent; Pfeiffer, Weyland; Pollak, James E. Peace Corps.
- R Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  Robison, Howard W.; Rockwell, George H.; Rockwell, Mary Palmer; Rubenstein, Jerome S. Rochester Institute of Technology; Rockefeller Foundation; Student deportment.
- S Miscellaneous., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  Sack, Henri S.; Saffeir, Harvey; Detweiler, A. Henry. Sardis Expedition.
- 8 Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  Scheraga, H. A.; Senior, Maud; Sloan, Alfred P.; Stephens, Thomas E. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
- T Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  Tuller, J. D.; Kahn, Alfred E. Dept. of Economics.
- Teeigle Foundation., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- U Miscellaneous., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  Uris, Harold D.; Mints, Isaak I. Uris Library; USSR.
- W Miscellaneous., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  Wilson, Arthur W.
- Northeastern Water Pollution Control Research Facility., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
  Fitzpatrick, Paul; Donlon, Mary H.
- Board of Trustees - Random Notes., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Cisler, Walker L.; Dean, Arthur H., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Dean, Arthur H., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Dean, Arthur H.; Donlon, Mary H.; Cornell, Mary., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  Noyes, Nicholas H.; Vail, Malcolm D.; Olin, John M.; Olin, Spencer T. Lilly Endowment; Cornell Alumni Fund.
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees. Scheetz, Francis H.; Tuller, J. D.; Severinghaus, Leslie R.; Wood, Frederic C., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Board of Trustees - Individual Trustees., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
  Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Lipchitz, Jacques; Boynton, Damon.
- Board of Trustees - Floyd R. Newman. Helen Newman Hall., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Administrative Staff Minutes., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Administrative Staff Minutes., 1959-63 (Box 29, Folder 29-35)
- Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure. Greisen, Kenneth., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Office of the Provost., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Vice President for University Development., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  Zwingle, J. L.
- Office of the Director of the Budget. McKeegan, Paul L.; Teagle, Walter C. Graduate School of Nutrition., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Office of the University Counsel., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  Stamp, Neal R.; McHugh, William F. Secretary of the Corporation.
- Office of Admissions., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Office of the Controller., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Counselor of Foreign Students., 1959-62 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  Blackall, Eric A.; Williams, David B.
- Fraternities and Sororities., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  Interfraternity Council; Small Group Housing Report.
- Executive Board of Student Government. Vogelesang, Sandra L., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Cornell University Library., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  McCarthy, Stephen A.; Dean, Arthur H.; Gottschalk, Louis; Reichmann, Felix; Uris, Harold D.; Lipchitz, Jacques. Satinsky Collection on Lincoln and Lincolniana; Lavoisier Collection; Lafayette Collection.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art. Kuck, Harry H., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- University Faculty., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  Committee on Student Affairs.
- University Lectures., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  Fischer, George. Committee on Soviet Studies; USSR.
- Committee on Scheduling Public Events., 1951 (Box 29, Folder 50)
- Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure. Greisen, Kenneth., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 51)
- New York State College of Agriculture. Palm, Charles E. University of the Philippines; Ford Foundation., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 52)
- New York State College of Agriculture. Palm, Charles E. National Science Foundation; International Agricultural Development; University of the Philippines; Rockefeller Foundation., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 53)
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  Palm, Charles E.; Rockwell, George H.; Kennedy, W. Keith. National Science Foundation; Committee on Botanical Resources and Needs.
- Division of Life Sciences (Proposed)., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 55)
- Dept. of Conservation., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  Swanson, Gustav A.; Greenewalt, Crawford H.
- Laboratory of Ornithology., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  Sibley, Charles G.
- College of Architecture., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  Kelly, Burnham.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 59)
- College of Arts and Sciences -Departments., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  Demorest, Jean-Jacques; Arnold, Carroll C. Dept. of Zoology; Dept. of Romance Literature; Dept. of Speech and Drama.
- Glee Club., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 61)
- Center for International Studies., 1961-63 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  Muller, Steven; Einaudi, Mario. Conference on Problems of Hemisphere Security; Ford Foundation.
- New York State College of Home Economics. Ghana., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 63)
- New York State Veterinary College., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  Poppensiek, George C.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1962 (Box 29, Folder 65)
- School of Hotel Administration., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 66)
- School of Education., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 67)
- ROTC., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 68)
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 69)
- Ivy League., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 70)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 71)
  Ross, Ira G.
- Summer Session., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 72)
  Smith, W. A. National Science Foundation.
- Cornell Plantations., 1961-62 (Box 29, Folder 73)
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 74)
- Danforth Foundation., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 75)
- Cornell Alumni Fund., n.d. (Box 29, Folder 76)
- New York State Education Dept., 1962-63 (Box 29, Folder 77)
- College of Architecture Deanship., 1960 (Box 29, Folder 78)
- School of Hotel Administration Deanship., 1960 (Box 29, Folder 79-83)
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration Deanship., 1961 (Box 29, Folder 84-95)
- Personal correspondence of Deane W. Malott while president of Cornell University
  - Africa., 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Gubb, Larry E.; Gubb, Helen; Block, Jack.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1953-63 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Merdes, Edward A.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1952-63 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Alien, George E.; Alien, Edward W. American Airlines.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1957-61 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Bachrach, Louis Fabian; Baker, John C.; Ball, William H.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1953-63 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1952-61 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1957-63 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Briggs, Ellis 0.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1951-63 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Browns, R. Edwin. Bryant College.
  - University of California., 1954-55 (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
  - C Miscellaneous., 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Carlson, Frank.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1959-62 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Clark, Marguerite L.
  - C Miscellaneous. McCay, Clive M., 1952-62 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - C Miscellaneous., 1957-63 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Bohemian Grove.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1952-62 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1953-63 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Dole, James D.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1953-58 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - E Miscellaneous., 1953-62 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    Eisenhower, Dwight D.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1957-63 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Parley, Hugh D.; Farquhar, Francis P. Bohemian Grove.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1955-62 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Faus, Warren W.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1956-62 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    Fisher, John W.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Gaston, William; Glenn, Frank.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1955-61 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    Goheen, Robert F.; Greenewalt, Crawford H.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1956-63 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Gaunt lett, John H.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1958-63 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - H Miscellaneous., 1956-62 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Hillary, Edmund.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1952-54 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of Government (Hoover Commission).
  - I Miscellaneous., 1956-61 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    Imes, Adelaide Dick. Ithaca College.
  - J Miscellaneous., 1956-62 (Box 30, Folder 29-30)
    Johnson, Ralph B.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1951-61 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    Kay, Harold T.; Kennedy, John F.; Sullivan, Frank. Sullivan article about White and Cornell.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1957-63 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    Kiaer, Hans Th.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1955-63 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    Landon, Alf M.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1956-63 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    Landon, Alf M.; Lapham, Helen; Lee, Ivy.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1954-62 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    Litchfield, Edward H.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1958-63 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    McGreevy, Milton.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1954-63 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    McLaughlin, Drew.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1951-59 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    Malott, Robert H.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    Malotte, Deen C.; Marks, A. Lester.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1954-63 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    Mehta, Ved; Menjou, Adolph J.; Merner, Gar field David.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1958-62 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Deane W. Malott - Personal., 1959-62 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - N Miscellaneous., 1956-60 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    Nixon, Richard M.; Nowell, Alien M.